coralixthemes.com 2017-12-16

# Privacy - Coralix Themes

CoralixThemes (SITE) has established this privacy policy to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy of the users of our website. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy, and how we treat personally identifiable information collected from our visitors and users. While this isn’t the most glamorous of documents, privacy is a big concern these days, and we take it very seriously for you, our valued visitors.

#### WHAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVERS

This privacy policy covers CoralixThemes treatment of personally identifiable information collected by CoralixThemes through a website owned and operated by CoralixThemes. This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies that CoralixThemes does not own or control, or of persons that CoralixThemes does not employ or manage, including any third-party content contributors bound by contract and any third-party websites to which the SITE may link.

#### COLLECTION & USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

You can visit the website of CoralixThemes without revealing any personal information. However, CoralixThemes needs certain personal information if you wish to purchase certain products, receive our newsletter, or use certain CoralixThemes services.

Where required, this information may include your personal contact information and/or your company contact information. CoralixThemes will use this information to reply to your inquiries, to provide you with requested products and services, and to contact you regarding new products and services. By accessing the services of CoralixThemes and voluntarily providing us with the requested personal information, you consent to the collection and use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

#### COLLECTION & USE OF NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION

CoralixThemes automatically receives and records non-personal information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you requested. CoralixThemes may use this information to customize the content you see and to fulfill your requests for certain products and services. However, CoralixThemes does not connect this non-personal data to any personal information collected from you.

#### INFORMATION SHARING & DISCLOSURE

CoralixThemes will not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### CONSENT

If you do not consent to the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information as outlined in this policy, please do not provide any personal information to CoralixThemes. If you have provided personal information to CoralixThemes and no longer consent to its use or disclosure as outlined herein, please notify us.

#### SECURITY

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be considered 100% secure. However, your CoralixThemes information is protected for your privacy and security. In certain areas of our websites, as identified on the site, CoralixThemes may use industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions. We also safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access through access control procedures and physical security measures. Further, CoralixThemes retains your personal information only as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes identified above or as required by law.

#### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

CoralixThemes may at any time, without notice to you and in its sole discretion, amend this policy from time to time. When it does, CoralixThemes will also revise the “last update” date at the top of this Privacy Policy. Please review this policy periodically. Your continued use of the SITE after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof.

#### QUESTIONS OR SUGGESTIONS

If you have questions or suggestions about this privacy policy, or your own personal information, please contact us directly.
